<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="org.modelgoon"
      label="ModelGoon"
      version="4.3.0"
      provider-name="ModelGoon">

   <description url="http://www.modelgoon.org">
      ModelGoon brings visual UML Models into the Java world.
   </description>

   <copyright url="http://www.modelgoon.org">
      Copyright (c) 2010-2011 ModelGoon Contributors. All rights reserved.
   </copyright>

   <license url="http://www.modelgoon.org">
      License
ModelGoon UML4Java LICENSE
Copyright (c) 2010-2011 ModelGoon Contributors. All rights reserved.
Permission to use, copy, modify, and distribute this software
in source or binary form for any purpose with or without fee
is hereby granted, provided that the following conditions are
met:
1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright
notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer
in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the
distribution.
3. Redistributions of modified versions and/or work based on
this software requires the specific prior written permission of the
author and must anyway let their source files be available publicly.
4. Neither the name of ModelGoon nor the names of its contributors
may be used to endorse or promote products derived from this
software without specific prior written permission.
THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE REGENTS AND CONTRIBUTORS &quot;AS
IS&quot; AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT
LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS
FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
REGENTS OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL,
SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT
NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES;
LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER
CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT
LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING
IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF
THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
   </license>

   <url>
      <discovery label="ModelGoon&apos;s Website" url="http://www.modelgoon.org"/>
   </url>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.gef"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="org.modelgoon.plugin"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
